Guide to the Time Inc. People Publishing and Business Records 1973-2003 MS 3009-RG 27
New-York Historical Society
- Series I. Publisher Richard Durrell Files, 1973-1983; 56.25 Linear feet in 57 record cartons
  - Subseries I.B. Subject Files, 1973-1983; 55.25 Linear feet in 56 record cartons
    - Nashville: October 5-7, 1979 (Offsite-box 2966, Folder 7)
    - National Enquirer, 1979 (Offsite-box 2966, Folder 8)
    - National Golf Links, 1979 (Offsite-box 2966, Folder 9)
    - National Star, 1979 (Offsite-box 2966, Folder 10)
    - Newsstand Draw and Sale, 1979 (Offsite-box 2966, Folder 11)
    - New York Times, 1979 (Offsite-box 2966, Folder 12)
    - Newsweek, 1979 (Offsite-box 2966, Folder 13)
    - Offset, 1979 (Offsite-box 2966, Folder 14)
    - Out of Town Schedules, 1979 (Offsite-box 2966, Folder 15)
    - Paper Shortage, 1979 (Offsite-box 2966, Folder 16)
    - Paper Shortage: Supercalendered, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 2966, Folder 17-19)
    - Parties, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 2966, Folder 20)
    - Parties: Valentine's Day: Roseland: February 14, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 2966, Folder 21)
    - Parties: Fifth Anniversary Party: March 8, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 2966, Folder 22)
    - Parties: Stan Posthorn: May 9, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 2966, Folder 23)
    - Parties: Lund and Hodgekiss: June 21, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 2966, Folder 24)
    - Parties: San Francisco Opening Party: August 22, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 2966, Folder 25)
    - People Shopper, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 2966, Folder 26)
    - People to People, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 2966, Folder 27)
    - Permissions, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 2966, Folder 28)
    - Personnel, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 2966, Folder 29)
    - Personnel: Promotion Director Probe, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 2966, Folder 30)
    - Photographers, Fees, Etc., 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 2966, Folder 31)
    - Playboy Enterprises, Inc., 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 2966, Folder 32)
    - Positioning, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 2966, Folder 33)
    - Postal Service, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 2966, Folder 34)
    - Posters, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 2966, Folder 35)
    - Posters [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Offsite-box R42)
    - Presentations, 1979 (Offsite-box 2967, Folder 1)
    - Presentations: Food Category: Food Marketing Institute, 1979 (Offsite-box 2967, Folder 2)
    - Presentations: Industry, 1979 (Offsite-box 2967, Folder 3)
    - Presentations: People's Choice, 1979 (Offsite-box 2967, Folder 4)
    - Presentations: Synergistic, 1979 (Offsite-box 2967, Folder 5)
    - Price Tests, 1979 (Offsite-box 2967, Folder 6)
    - Pricing, Regulations, Tests, Etc., 1979 (Offsite-box 2967, Folder 7)
    - Printing: Plants: Pine Street, 1979 (Offsite-box 2967, Folder 8)
    - Production, 1979 (Offsite-box 2967, Folder 9)
    - Promotion: Air: Commercials, 1979 (Offsite-box 2967, Folder 10)
    - Promotion: Circulation Agency Search, 1979 (Offsite-box 2967, Folder 11-12)
    - Promotion: Circulation Subscription Cards, 1979 (Offsite-box 2967, Folder 13)
    - Promotion: Consumer Circulation, 1979 (Offsite-box 2967, Folder 14)
    - Promotion: Consumer Radio, 1979 (Offsite-box 2967, Folder 15)
    - Promotion: General, 1979 (Offsite-box 2967, Folder 16)
    - Promotion: Print, 1979 (Offsite-box 2967, Folder 17)
    - Promotion: Television, 1979 (Offsite-box 2967, Folder 18)
    - Publicity: Air, 1979 (Offsite-box 2967, Folder 19)
    - Publicity: General, 1979 (Offsite-box 2967, Folder 20)
    - Publicity: Print, 1979 (Offsite-box 2967, Folder 21)
    - Publisher's Lunch, 1979 (Offsite-box 2967, Folder 22)
    - Raises, 1979 (Offsite-box 2967, Folder 23)
    - Rate Base, 1979 (Offsite-box 2967, Folder 24)
    - Rate Increase, 1979 (Offsite-box 2967, Folder 25)
    - Rates, 1979 (Offsite-box 2967, Folder 26)
    - Rates: Subscriptions [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2967, Folder 27)
    - Reader's Digest, 1979 (Offsite-box 2967, Folder 28)
    - Research, 1979 (Offsite-box 2967, Folder 29)
    - Research: American Association of Advertising Agencies, 1979 (Offsite-box 2967, Folder 30)
    - Research: Focus Groups, 1979 (Offsite-box 2967, Folder 31)
    - Research: Focus Groups: Atlanta: March 22-24, 1979 (Offsite-box 2967, Folder 32)
    - Research: Focus Groups: Hartford: June 28-29, 1979 (Offsite-box 2967, Folder 33)
    - Research: Focus Groups: Long Island: August 7-8, 1979 (Offsite-box 2967, Folder 34)
    - Research: Focus Groups: Ridgewood, New Jersey: December 18, 1979 (Offsite-box 2967, Folder 35)
    - Research: People Buyer Survey, 1979 (Offsite-box 2968, Folder 1)
    - Research: Readers Perception Study, 1979 (Offsite-box 2968, Folder 2)
    - Research: Telmar, 1979 (Offsite-box 2968, Folder 3)
    - Result Stories, 1979 (Offsite-box 2968, Folder 4)
    - RFK Pro-Celebrity Tournament, 1979 (Offsite-box 2968, Folder 5)
    - Sales Figures, 1979 (Offsite-box 2968, Folder 6)
    - Sales Meeting: Hawaii: May 16-21, 1979 (Offsite-box 2968, Folder 7)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Crowley, John, 1979 (Offsite-box 2968, Folder 8)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Durrell, Dick, 1979 (Offsite-box 2968, Folder 9)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Gentalen, Tiit, 1979 (Offsite-box 2968, Folder 10)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Lund, Chuck, 1979 (Offsite-box 2968, Folder 11)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Miscellaneous, 1979 (Offsite-box 2968, Folder 12)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Motta, Tony, 1979 (Offsite-box 2968, Folder 13)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Nelson, Bill, 1979 (Offsite-box 2968, Folder 14)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Promotion, 1979 (Offsite-box 2968, Folder 15)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Schenck, John, 1979 (Offsite-box 2968, Folder 16)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Thomas, Dick, 1979 (Offsite-box 2968, Folder 17)
    - Screenings:, 1979 (Offsite-box 2968, Folder 18)
    - Screenings: Dracula: July 9-10, 1979 (Offsite-box 2968, Folder 19)
    - Serialization, 1979 (Offsite-box 2968, Folder 20)
    - Simmons, 1979 (Offsite-box 2968, Folder 21)
    - Simmons Market Research Bureau, 1979 (Offsite-box 2968, Folder 22)
    - Special Units, 1979 (Offsite-box 2968, Folder 23)
    - Speeches: Philadelphia: August 15, 1979 (Offsite-box 2968, Folder 24)
    - Starch, 1979 (Offsite-box 2968, Folder 25)
    - Store Checks, 1979 (Offsite-box 2968, Folder 26)
    - Store Checks by Salesmen, 1979 (Offsite-box 2968, Folder 27)
    - Subscriptions, 1979 (Offsite-box 2968, Folder 28)
    - Subscriptions: Test, 1979 (Offsite-box 2968, Folder 29)
    - Syndication, 1979 (Offsite-box 2968, Folder 30)
    - Teamsters Strike, 1979 (Offsite-box 2968, Folder 31)
    - Temple-Eastex, 1979 (Offsite-box 2968, Folder 32)
    - Test Markets, 1979 (Offsite-box 2968, Folder 33)
    - Television and TV Shows, 1979 (Offsite-box 2968, Folder 34)
    - Television and TV Shows: Susskind, David, 1979 (Offsite-box 2968, Folder 35)
    - Time Distribution Services: A & P, 1979 (Offsite-box 2968, Folder 36)
    - Time Distribution Services: Bonus, 1979 (Offsite-box 2968, Folder 37)
    - Time Distribution Services: Bus Stop/Poster Campaign: Young & Rubicam, 1979 (Offsite-box 2968, Folder 38)
    - Time Distribution Services: Checkers, 1979 (Offsite-box 2968, Folder 39)
    - Time Distribution Services: Checkout, 1979 (Offsite-box 2969, Folder 1)
    - Time Distribution Services: Correspondence, 1979 (Offsite-box 2969, Folder 2)
    - Time Distribution Services: General, 1979 (Offsite-box 2969, Folder 3)
    - Time Distribution Services: Meeting: Miami: January 23-24, 1979 (Offsite-box 2969, Folder 4)
    - Time Distribution Services: Meeting: Dallas: May 9, 1979 (Offsite-box 2969, Folder 5)
    - Time Distribution Services: Meeting: Sterling Forest: June 27-29, 1979 (Offsite-box 2969, Folder 6)
    - Time Distribution Services: Meeting: Phoenix: November 6, 1979 (Offsite-box 2969, Folder 7)
    - Time Distribution Services: Monthly and Weekly Report, 1979 (Offsite-box 2969, Folder 8)
    - Time Distribution Services: People, 1979 (Offsite-box 2969, Folder 9)
    - Time Distribution Services: Personnel, 1979 (Offsite-box 2969, Folder 10)
    - Time Distribution Services: Racking, 1979 (Offsite-box 2969, Folder 11)
    - Time Distribution Services: Racking: Stories Covered Weekly, 1979 (Offsite-box 2969, Folder 12)
    - Time Distribution Services: Stores, 1979 (Offsite-box 2969, Folder 14)
    - Time Distribution Services: Stores: Jewel, 1979 (Offsite-box 2969, Folder 15)
    - Time Distribution Services: Safeway, 1979 (Offsite-box 2969, Folder 13)
    - Time Distribution Services: Test: Burbank, California Agency, 1979 (Offsite-box 2969, Folder 16)
    - Time Distribution Services: Wholesalers, 1979 (Offsite-box 2969, Folder 17)
    - Time Distribution Services: Wholesalers: Cities Off Certification, 1979 (Offsite-box 2969, Folder 18)
    - Time Distribution Services: Wholesalers: Late Delivery Reports, 1979 (Offsite-box 2969, Folder 19)
    - Trades, 1979 (Offsite-box 2969, Folder 20)
    - United Way, 1979 (Offsite-box 2969, Folder 21)
    - Us, 1979 (Offsite-box 2969, Folder 22)
    - Us: Circulation, 1979 (Offsite-box 2969, Folder 23)
    - Us: Promotion, 1979 (Offsite-box 2969, Folder 24)
    - Us: Publicity, 1979 (Offsite-box 2969, Folder 25)
    - Us: Research, 1979 (Offsite-box 2969, Folder 26)
    - Us: Sales Figures, 1979 (Offsite-box 2969, Folder 27)
    - Vacations, 1979 (Offsite-box 2969, Folder 28)
    - Washington Star, 1979 (Offsite-box 2969, Folder 29)
    - Weekly Regional Managers Sales Estimate, 1979 (Offsite-box 2969, Folder 30)
    - Weekly Regional Managers Sales Estimate: Us, 1979 (Offsite-box 2969, Folder 31)
    - Weekly Report, 1979 (Offsite-box 2969, Folder 32-33)
    - Wholesalers: Charles Levy Circulation Company, 1979 (Offsite-box 2969, Folder 34)
    - Women, 1979 (Offsite-box 2969, Folder 35)
    - Women's Books, 1979 (Offsite-box 2970, Folder 1)
    - Women's Day, 1979 (Offsite-box 2970, Folder 2)
    - Year-End Guesstimates: 1979 (Offsite-box 2970, Folder 3)
    - Year-End Guesstimates: 1978: By January 15, 1979 (Offsite-box 2970, Folder 4)
    - Year End Issue, 1979 (Offsite-box 2970, Folder 5)
    - Young & Rubicam Promotion, 1979 (Offsite-box 2970, Folder 6)
    - Branch Offices: Chicago, 1979 (Offsite-box 2970, Folder 7)
    - Branch Offices: Columbus: April 24-25, 1979 (Offsite-box 2970, Folder 8)
    - Branch Offices: Detroit, 1979 (Offsite-box 2970, Folder 9)
    - Branch Offices: Los Angeles, 1979 (Offsite-box 2970, Folder 10)
    - Branch Offices: New York, 1979 (Offsite-box 2970, Folder 11)
    - Branch Offices: San Francisco, 1979 (Offsite-box 2970, Folder 12)
    - Branch Offices: Washington, D.C., 1979 (Offsite-box 2970, Folder 13)
    - Branch Offices: West Coast, 1979 (Offsite-box 2970, Folder 14)
    - Ad Council, 1980 (Offsite-box 2970, Folder 15)
    - Ad Director's Memoranda, 1980 (Offsite-box 2970, Folder 16)
    - Advertising/Edit Ratio, 1980 (Offsite-box 2970, Folder 17)
    - Advertising Records, 1980 (Offsite-box 2970, Folder 18)
    - Advertising Research Foundation, 1980 (Offsite-box 2970, Folder 19)
    - Affirmative Action, 1980 (Offsite-box 2970, Folder 20)
    - Agency Reports [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2970, Folder 21)
    - Airline Research [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2970, Folder 22)
    - Airport Sale, 1980 (Offsite-box 2970, Folder 23)
    - Airline Subscriptions, 1980 (Offsite-box 2970, Folder 24)
    - American Advertising Federation, 1980 (Offsite-box 2970, Folder 25-26)
    - Annual Report, 1980 (Offsite-box 2970, Folder 27)
    - Apparel Category, 1980 (Offsite-box 2970, Folder 28)
    - Applications, 1980 (Offsite-box 2970, Folder 29-31)
    - Association of National Advertisers, 1980 (Offsite-box 2970, Folder 32)
    - Audit Bureau of Circulation Reports: 1975-1980 (Offsite-box 2970, Folder 33-35)
    - Audit Bureau of Circulation Reports: 1975-1980 (Offsite-box 2971, Folder 1-2)
    - Automotive Category, 1980 (Offsite-box 2971, Folder 3)
    - Awards, 1980 (Offsite-box 2971, Folder 4)
    - Background, 1980 (Offsite-box 2971, Folder 5)
    - Bagley Report: Food Marketing Institute, 1980 (Offsite-box 2971, Folder 6)
    - Baseball Lists, Etc., 1980 (Offsite-box 2971, Folder 7)
    - Basketball Lists, 1980 (Offsite-box 2971, Folder 8)
    - Bios, 1980 (Offsite-box 2971, Folder 9)
    - Bios [RESTRICTED], 1980 (Offsite-box R42)
    - Bleed, 1980 (Offsite-box 2971, Folder 10)
    - Blynn, Buz: Miami Representative, 1980 (Offsite-box 2971, Folder 11)
    - Body: Edit Section: Diet/Fitness, 1980 (Offsite-box 2971, Folder 12)
    - Bonus Letters, 1980 (Offsite-box 2971, Folder 13)
    - Budget: 1981, 1980 (Offsite-box 2971, Folder 14)
    - Budget: Ad Sales, 1980 (Offsite-box 2971, Folder 15)
    - Budget: Edit [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2971, Folder 16)
    - Budget and Five Year Plan, 1980 (Offsite-box 2971, Folder 17-19)
    - Budget: General, 1980 (Offsite-box 2971, Folder 20)
    - Budget: Marketing Services and Research, 1980 (Offsite-box 2971, Folder 21)
    - Budget: Promotion, 1980 (Offsite-box 2971, Folder 22)
    - Cable Television, 1980 (Offsite-box 2971, Folder 23)
    - Cambodia Campaigns, 1980 (Offsite-box 2971, Folder 24)
    - Cambridge, 1980 (Offsite-box 2971, Folder 25)
    - Canada, 1980 (Offsite-box 2971, Folder 26)
    - Cancer Story, 1980 (Offsite-box 2971, Folder 27)
    - Cigarette Category, 1980 (Offsite-box 2971, Folder 28)
    - Circulation, 1980 (Offsite-box 2971, Folder 29)
    - Circulation: All Magazines, 1980 (Offsite-box 2971, Folder 30)
    - Circulation: Red Tag, 1980 (Offsite-box 2971, Folder 31)
    - Clips: Background Material, 1980 (Offsite-box 2971, Folder 32)
    - Clips: Box Stores, 1980 (Offsite-box 2971, Folder 33)
    - Clips: Cutback in Buying, Etc., 1980 (Offsite-box 2971, Folder 34)
    - Clips: People, 1980 (Offsite-box 2971, Folder 35)
    - Clips: Supermarket, 1980 (Offsite-box 2972, Folder 1)
    - College Market, 1980 (Offsite-box 2972, Folder 2)
    - Color Costs, 1980 (Offsite-box 2972, Folder 3)
    - Comp Lists, 1980 (Offsite-box 2972, Folder 4)
    - Company Plane, 1980 (Offsite-box 2972, Folder 5)
    - Complaints: Advertising, Etc., 1980 (Offsite-box 2972, Folder 6)
    - Complaint Reports: Jerry Stelle, 1980 (Offsite-box 2972, Folder 7-8)
    - Conventions: Political, 1980 (Offsite-box 2972, Folder 9)
    - Conventions: Second Half, 1980 (Offsite-box 2972, Folder 10-11)
    - Conventions: Trade, Etc., 1980 (Offsite-box 2972, Folder 12)
    - Conventions: Food Marketing Institute: Las Vegas: February 10-13, 1980 (Offsite-box 2972, Folder 13)
    - Conventions: Food Marketing Institute: Las Vegas: February 10: Invitees, 1980 (Offsite-box 2972, Folder 14)
    - Conventions: Western Association of Food Chains: Phoenix: April 19-24, 1980 (Offsite-box 2972, Folder 15)
    - Conventions: Food Marketing Institute: Dallas: May 4-7, 1980 (Offsite-box 2972, Folder 16)
    - Conventions: American Association of Advertising Agencies: May 14-17, 1980 (Offsite-box 2972, Folder 17)
    - Conventions: Republican Convention: Detroit: July 14, 1980 (Offsite-box 2972, Folder 18)
    - Conventions: Democratic Convention: New York: August 11, 1980 (Offsite-box 2972, Folder 19)
    - Conventions: National Association of Chain Stores: Honolulu: October 4-9, 1980 (Offsite-box 2972, Folder 20)
    - Conventions: Food Marketing Institute: October 19-21, 1980 (Offsite-box 2972, Folder 21-22)
    - Copy Acceptance, 1980 (Offsite-box 2972, Folder 23)
    - Copy Processing: Decentralization, 1980 (Offsite-box 2972, Folder 24)
    - Corporate Manufacturing and Distribution, 1980 (Offsite-box 2972, Folder 25)
    - Corporate Manufacturing and Distribution: CPDA, 1980 (Offsite-box 2972, Folder 26)
    - Corporate Manufacturing and Distributing: Letterpress/Offset, 1980 (Offsite-box 2972, Folder 27)
    - Cosmopolitan, 1980 (Offsite-box 2972, Folder 28)
    - Couponing, 1980 (Offsite-box 2972, Folder 29)
    - Covers, 1980 (Offsite-box 2972, Folder 30)
    - Covers: Other Magazines, 1980 (Offsite-box 2972, Folder 31)
    - Covers: Tip-Ons [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2972, Folder 32)
    - Covers: Tests and Research, 1980 (Offsite-box 2972, Folder 33)
    - CPM, 1980 (Offsite-box 2973, Folder 1)
    - Doonesbury, 1980 (Offsite-box 2973, Folder 2)
    - Delivery Reports, 1980 (Offsite-box 2973, Folder 3)
    - Direct Mail, 1980 (Offsite-box 2973, Folder 4)
    - Direct Response Advertising [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2973, Folder 5)
    - Discover, 1980 (Offsite-box 2973, Folder 6)
    - Distribution, 1980 (Offsite-box 2973, Folder 7)
    - Douglas, Mike Show, 1980 (Offsite-box 2973, Folder 8)
    - Edit: Close, 1980 (Offsite-box 2973, Folder 9)
    - Edit: Close and Misses [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2973, Folder 10)
    - Edit: Color, 1980 (Offsite-box 2973, Folder 11)
    - Edit: Pages, 1980 (Offsite-box 2973, Folder 12)
    - Edit: Production [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2973, Folder 13)
    - Edit: Serious People Articles, 1980 (Offsite-box 2973, Folder 14)
    - Edit: Windows On The World, 1980 (Offsite-box 2973, Folder 15)
    - Esquire, 1980 (Offsite-box 2973, Folder 16)
    - Evaluations, 1980 (Offsite-box 2973, Folder 17)
    - Fact Sheets, 1980 (Offsite-box 2973, Folder 18)
    - Family Circle, 1980 (Offsite-box 2973, Folder 19)
    - East Close, 1980 (Offsite-box 2973, Folder 20)
    - Federal Trade Commission [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2973, Folder 21)
    - Figures [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2973, Folder 22)
    - Filler Space, 1980 (Offsite-box 2973, Folder 23)
    - Filler Space: Others in People, 1980 (Offsite-box 2973, Folder 24)
    - Five Year Plan, 1980 (Offsite-box 2973, Folder 25)
    - Folio, 1980 (Offsite-box 2973, Folder 26)
    - Food Category, 1980 (Offsite-box 2973, Folder 27)
    - Fortune, 1980 (Offsite-box 2973, Folder 28)
    - Free Contribution Requests, 1980 (Offsite-box 2973, Folder 29)
    - Free Space Requests, 1980 (Offsite-box 2973, Folder 30)
    - Free Subscription Requests [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2973, Folder 31)
    - Free: Young & Rubicam, 1980 (Offsite-box 2973, Folder 32)
    - Gallagher Reports, 1980 (Offsite-box 2973, Folder 33)
    - Golf, 1980 (Offsite-box 2973, Folder 34)
    - Golf: Time Inc. Invitational: May 19, 1980 (Offsite-box 2973, Folder 35)
    - Golf: Golden Lights: May 28, 1980 (Offsite-box 2973, Folder 36)
    - Golf: Time Inc. Invitational: Art Keylor: Maidstone: June 23-24, 1980 (Offsite-box 2973, Folder 37)
    - Golf: Blind Brook: Alaska: July 15, 1980 (Offsite-box 2973, Folder 38)
    - Golf: Tuxedo: July 17, 1980 (Offsite-box 2973, Folder 39)
    - Golf: Time Inc. Invitational: September 15-16, 1980 (Offsite-box 2973, Folder 40)
    - Golf: Time Inc. Invitational: Palm Springs: December 3-6, 1980 (Offsite-box 2973, Folder 41)
    - Good Housekeeping, 1980 (Offsite-box 2973, Folder 42)
    - Grant Gentry, 1980 (Offsite-box 2973, Folder 43)
    - HABA Category, 1980 (Offsite-box 2973, Folder 44)
    - Hall Magazine Editorial Report, 1980 (Offsite-box 2973, Folder 45)
    - HBA Category, 1980 (Offsite-box 2973, Folder 46)
    - Hold, 1980 (Offsite-box 2973, Folder 47)
    - Home Box Office, 1980 (Offsite-box 2973, Folder 48-49)
    - Home Furnishings Category [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2973, Folder 50)
    - House Space Orders, 1980 (Offsite-box 2973, Folder 51)
    - Ibit, 1980 (Offsite-box 2973, Folder 52)
    - Ideas, 1980 (Offsite-box 2974, Folder 1-2)
    - Ideas: Little Brown, 1980 (Offsite-box 2974, Folder 3)
    - Ideas: Murray Roberts, 1980 (Offsite-box 2974, Folder 4)
    - Ideas: Norbach, 1980 (Offsite-box 2974, Folder 5)
    - Ideas: Puzzle, 1980 (Offsite-box 2974, Folder 6)
    - Information Systems Division, 1980 (Offsite-box 2974, Folder 7)
    - Inserts, 1980 (Offsite-box 2974, Folder 8)
    - Insert Cards, 1980 (Offsite-box 2974, Folder 9)
    - Intercorporate Group, 1980 (Offsite-box 2974, Folder 10)
    - International, 1980 (Offsite-box 2974, Folder 11)
    - International: England, 1980 (Offsite-box 2974, Folder 12)
    - International: Japan, 1980 (Offsite-box 2974, Folder 13)
    - International: Japan [RESTRICTED], 1980 (Offsite-box R42)
    - Legal, 1980 (Offsite-box 2974, Folder 14)
    - Legal: Logo, 1980 (Offsite-box 2974, Folder 15)
    - Legal: Trademark, 1980 (Offsite-box 2974, Folder 16)
    - Letters, 1980 (Offsite-box 2974, Folder 17)
    - Letters: Circulation Complaints, 1980 (Offsite-box 2974, Folder 18)
    - Letters: Complaints on Edit, 1980 (Offsite-box 2974, Folder 19)
    - Letters: Miscellaneous, 1980 (Offsite-box 2974, Folder 20)
    - Letters: Northland College, 1980 (Offsite-box 2974, Folder 21-24)
    - Letters: Per Person vs. Billing, 1980 (Offsite-box 2974, Folder 25)
    - Letters: Personal, 1980 (Offsite-box 2974, Folder 26-27)
    - Letters: Personal: Arthritis Foundation, 1980 (Offsite-box 2974, Folder 28-29)
    - Letters: Pricing, 1980 (Offsite-box 2974, Folder 30)
    - Letters: Re: August 11 Cover, 1980 (Offsite-box 2974, Folder 31)
    - Letters: Reports, 1980 (Offsite-box 2974, Folder 32)
    - Letters: Reports: Second Half, 1980 (Offsite-box 2975, Folder 1)
    - Letters: Requests for Edit Coverage, 1980 (Offsite-box 2975, Folder 2)
    - Letters: Too Much Advertising, 1980 (Offsite-box 2975, Folder 3)
    - Licensing [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2975, Folder 4)
    - Life, 1980 (Offsite-box 2975, Folder 5)
    - Liquor Category, 1980 (Offsite-box 2975, Folder 6)
    - Look [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2975, Folder 7)
    - Luncheons, Dinners, 1980 (Offsite-box 2975, Folder 8)
    - Luncheons/Dinners: Dan Shedrick Proposals [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2975, Folder 9)
    - Luncheons/Dinners: Baltimore Lunch, Washington Dinner: January 9, 1980 (Offsite-box 2975, Folder 10)
    - Luncheons/Dinners: Willie Stargell: January 10-11, 1980 (Offsite-box 2975, Folder 11)
    - Luncheons/Dinners: Dr. Arthur Schlesinger: February 5, 1980 (Offsite-box 2975, Folder 12)
    - Luncheons/Dinners: Edward S. Finkelstein Lunch: February 21, 1980 (Offsite-box 2975, Folder 13)
    - Luncheons/Dinners: Herb Brooks: April 11, 1980 (Offsite-box 2975, Folder 14)
    - Luncheons/Dinners: Stanley Marcus: April 16, 1980 (Offsite-box 2975, Folder 15)
    - Luncheons/Dinners: Herb Brooks: Minneapolis: June 27, 1980 (Offsite-box 2975, Folder 16)
    - Luncheons/Dinners: Minneapolis: August 12-13, 1980 (Offsite-box 2975, Folder 17)
    - Luncheons/Dinners: Stanley Marcus: October 9, 1980 (Offsite-box 2975, Folder 18)
    - Luncheons/Dinners: "21": New York People: November 18, 1980 (Offsite-box 2975, Folder 19)
    - Madison Avenue, 1980 (Offsite-box 2975, Folder 20)
    - Magazine Research Inc., 1980 (Offsite-box 2975, Folder 21)
    - Magazines, 1980 (Offsite-box 2975, Folder 22)
    - Magazines, Tabloids, Newspapers, Etc., 1980 (Offsite-box 2975, Folder 23)
    - Mailings, 1980 (Offsite-box 2975, Folder 24)
    - Mailings: Desk Calendars for 1981, 1980-1981 (Offsite-box 2975, Folder 25)
    - Mailings: The Fifth Horseman, 1980-1981 (Offsite-box 2975, Folder 26-27)
    - Matthew Kelly Weekend, 1980-1981 (Offsite-box 2975, Folder 28)
    - McCall's, 1980-1981 (Offsite-box 2975, Folder 29)
    - Media Industry Newsletter, 1980-1981 (Offsite-box 2975, Folder 30)
    - Media Networks, Inc. [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2975, Folder 31)
    - Media Workshop [EMPTY] (Offsite-box 2975, Folder 32)
    - Mediamark Research Inc., 1980-1981 (Offsite-box 2975, Folder 33)
    - Meetings: General, 1980-1981 (Offsite-box 2975, Folder 34)
    - Memoranda: Cooper, Mike, 1980-1981 (Offsite-box 2975, Folder 35)
    - Memoranda: Crawford, Clare, 1980-1981 (Offsite-box 2975, Folder 36)
    - Memoranda: Crowley, John, 1980-1981 (Offsite-box 2975, Folder 37)
    - Memoranda: Crutcher, Larry, 1980-1981 (Offsite-box 2975, Folder 38)
    - Memoranda: Davidson, Ralph, 1980-1981 (Offsite-box 2975, Folder 39)
    - Memoranda: D'Onofrio, Pat: Share of Market Report, 1980-1981 (Offsite-box 2975, Folder 40)
    - Memoranda: Donovan, Hedley, 1980-1981 (Offsite-box 2975, Folder 41)
    - Memoranda: Edit, 1980-1981 (Offsite-box 2975, Folder 42)
    - Memoranda: Fisler, Bob, 1980 (Offsite-box 2976, Folder 1)